let savollar1 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "afraid",
        answer: "C. qo'rqqan",
        options: [
            "A. jaxldor",
            "B. dovyurak",
            "C. qo'rqqan",
            "D. uyalgan"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "to agree",
        answer: "A. qo'shilmoq",
        options: [
            "A. qo'shilmoq",
            "B. qarshi chiqmoq",
            "C. qo'shmoq",
            "D. anglamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "angry",
        answer: "B. jaxldor",
        options: [
            "A. g'amgin",
            "B. jaxldor",
            "C. baxtli",
            "D. hayratlangan"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "to arrive",
        answer: "D. yetib kelmoq",
        options: [
            "A. jo'nab ketmoq",
            "B. uchib ketmoq",
            "C. tark etmoq",
            "D. yetib kelmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "to attack",
        answer: "C. hujum qilmoq",
        options: [
            "A. himoya qilmoq",
            "B. baqirmoq",
            "C. hujum qilmoq",
            "D. asabiylashmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "bottom",
        answer: "A. past",
        options: [
            "A. past",
            "B. yuqori",
            "C. o'rta",
            "D. yon"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "clever",
        answer: "D. aqlli",
        options: [
            "A. ahmoq",
            "B. quvnoq",
            "C. qulay",
            "D. aqlli"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "cruel",
        answer: "C. zolim",
        options: [
            "A. yaxshi",
            "B. yomon",
            "C. zolim",
            "D. qiziq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "finally",
        answer: "B. vanihoyat",
        options: [
            "A. baxtimga",
            "B. vanihoyat",
            "C. keyin",
            "D. har doim"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "to hide",
        answer: "D. yashirmoq",
        options: [
            "A. ko'rsatmoq",
            "B. topmoq",
            "C. qo'ymoq",
            "D. yashirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "to hunt",
        answer: "C. ov qilmoq",
        options: [
            "A. quvmoq",
            "B. ushlamoq",
            "C. ov qilmoq",
            "D. tutmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "lot",
        answer: "A. ko'p",
        options: [
            "A. ko'p",
            "B. yetarli",
            "C. bir nechta",
            "D. bir qancha"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "middle",
        answer: "B. o'rta",
        options: [
            "A. past",
            "B. o'rta",
            "C. yuqori",
            "D. yon"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "moment",
        answer: "C. on",
        options: [
            "A. soat",
            "B. kun",
            "C. on",
            "D. hafta"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "pleased",
        answer: "D. baxtli",
        options: [
            "A. sokin",
            "B. asabiy",
            "C. omadli",
            "D. baxtli"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "to promise",
        answer: "B. va'da bermoq",
        options: [
            "A. qo'llab quvvatlamoq",
            "B. va'da bermoq",
            "C. buzmoq",
            "D. unutmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "to reply",
        answer: "C. javob bermoq",
        options: [
            "A. so'ramoq",
            "B. eslatmoq",
            "C. javob bermoq",
            "D. qaytarmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "safe",
        answer: "A. xavfsiz",
        options: [
            "A. xavfsiz",
            "B. yaroqli",
            "C. doimiy",
            "D. foydali"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "trick",
        answer: "D. hiyla",
        options: [
            "A. o'yin",
            "B. zavq",
            "C. hazil",
            "D. hiyla"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "well",
        answer: "C. yaxshi",
        options: [
            "A. yetarli",
            "B. qoniqarli",
            "C. yaxshi",
            "D. qiziq"
        ]
    }
];
